The president of every bank,
they're in that room.
So go in there and convince them
that you're strong.
I'm the largest independent
oil producer in the region.
The only difference
between me and Monty
is I'm meaner.
Underestimating me is how
I buy you out.
I'm assuming you know
the sharks are circling.
Yeah, and they leave
a pretty big wake.
500 barrels a day,
$10 million dollars a year.
And it's ours.
This is the dream?
I did it for you.
Seems like you've been given
priority walk-on status
with the cheerleading corps.
I got in?
You are president
of an oil company.
It's time you start
living like it.
We're on a fucking Gulfstream.
I am living it.
-Dorothy passed, T.L.
She's in a better place.
I'm sure you'll see her again.
If I do, that means
I'm in hell, too.
Who died?
My mother.
-Should be getting close.
-Yup.
We're approaching
target formation!
Pressure's really running now.
Buddy, your well's kicking.
-You think it or you know it?
-Gauges don't lie, buddy.
Got to shut the well
and activate the BOP.
I got it!
She's gonna blow!
I'm no geologist,
but I'd say that's
a pretty good place to drill.