[Tommy]
The president of every bank,
they're in that room.
So go in there and convince them
that you're strong.
I'm the largest independent
oil producer in the region.
The only difference
between me and Monty
is I'm meaner.
Underestimating me is how
I buy you out.
I'm assuming you know
the sharks are circling.
Yeah, and they leave
a pretty big wake.
[Cooper] 500 barrels a day,
$10 million dollars a year.
And it's ours.
This is the dream?
[Cooper]
I did it for you.
Seems like you've been given
priority walk-on status
with the cheerleading corps.
I got in? [gasps]
[Angela] You are president
of an oil company.
It's time you start
living like it.
We're on a fucking Gulfstream.
I am living it.
-Dorothy passed, T.L.
-[groans]
She's in a better place.
I'm sure you'll see her again.
If I do, that means
I'm in hell, too.
* dramatic music *
Who died?
My mother.
* To put it plain,
I just don't like you *
* Not a thing
about the way you is *
* And if there ever come a time
I got rabies *
* You're high
on my bitin' list *
* To put it plain,
I just don't like you *
* Not a thing
about the way you is *
* And if there ever come a time
I got rabies *
* You're high
on my bitin' list *
* Yeah, you're high
on the list *
* Of people getting bit
if they gave me a week or two *
* Before my brain
was so inflamed *
* The spirit left my shoes *
* I'd want to kiss my wife,
I'd want to hug my baby... *
-Should be getting close.
-Yup.
We're approaching
target formation!
Pressure's really running now.
Buddy, your well's kicking.
-You think it or you know it?
-Gauges don't lie, buddy.
Got to shut the well
and activate the BOP.
I got it!
She's gonna blow!
[metal creaking]
***
* To put it plain,
I just don't like you *
* I never really have
and I never really did *
* And if there ever
come a time I got rabies *
* You're high
on my bitin' list *
* Seizure fraught spinal rot *
* I'd want to be
with the ones I love *
* But in the light of the Moon,
with everybody sleeping *
* I'd draw me
a little bit of blood *
* With time so small,
my list ain't many *
* My list is short and few,
and the thing about it is *
* Everybody on the list
is coming in after you... *
I'm no geologist,
but I'd say that's
a pretty good place to drill.